http://www.dynamicimagingsolutions.com/corporate/data-privacy-policy.html

Password:
Email:
Contact Us
About Us
Corporate
Shipping PolicyReturn PolicyData & Privacy PolicyArtwork RequirementsQuality PolicyReseller InformationPayment Terms & Conditions
Services
Bar Code Support & ConsultationPre-Printing ServicesData ManagementBar Code Quality VerificationCustom ProgrammingBar Code FAQ for Libraries
Products
Library Bar Code Labels
Laminated Teslin Bar Code LabelsNon-Laminated Bar Code LabelsLaminated Paper Bar Code LabelsThermal Bar Code LabelsColour Bar Code Labels
Library Supplies
Spine Labels - SheetsSpine Labels - RollsPatron Cards & Key TagsLabel ProtectorsEM Security StripsDoor HangersRFID TagsRFID ReadersAllsop Strong BoxRemovable Hold LabelsBookmarks
Canada / US Customs
Customs FAQPARS, PAPS, B3'S, A8A'sCSA Cards
Custom Pre-Printed Labels
Warehouse Racking LabelsFreight Pro LabelsRetro-Reflective LabelsParts LabelsHarsh Environment Labels
Blank Labels
Thermal RollsLaser Sheets
Patron Cards & Key TagsScanners and Hardware
ScannersPrinters
Signage and Tags
Wobblers & DanglersShelftalkers
RFID Solutions
RFID TagsRFID Readers
Video Store LabelsVideo Supplies
EM Security StripsAllsop Strong Box
Markets
Library
Library Bar Code Labels
Laminated Teslin Bar Code LabelsNon-Laminated Bar Code LabelsLaminated Paper Bar Code LabelsThermal Bar Code LabelsColour Bar Code Labels
Library Supplies
Spine Labels - SheetsSpine Labels - RollsPatron Cards & Key TagsLabel ProtectorsEM Security StripsDoor HangersRFID TagsRFID ReadersAllsop Strong BoxRemovable Hold LabelsBookmarks
Blank Labels
Thermal RollsLaser Sheets
Patron Cards & Key Tags
Scanners and Hardware
ScannersPrinters
RFID Solutions
RFID TagsRFID Readers
Transportation
Custom Pre-Printed Labels
Warehouse Racking LabelsRetro-Reflective LabelsHarsh Environment Labels
Blank Labels
Thermal RollsLaser Sheets
Scanners and Hardware
ScannersPrinters
RFID Solutions
RFID TagsRFID Readers
VideoPatron Cards & Key Tags
Scanners and Hardware
RFID TagsRFID Readers
Corporate:
Shipping PolicyReturn PolicyData & Privacy PolicyArtwork RequirementsQuality PolicyReseller InformationPayment Terms & Conditions
Data & Privacy Policy
We value and respect our customer's information.  Dynamic Imaging Solutions Inc. will never sell your information to anyone, anytime, anywhere.
Dynamic Imaging Solutions may require or ask our customers to supply personal or confidential data when placing an order or producing a job. It is our policy to treat customer information and data as private and confidential, and we will not disclose this information, to other individuals or organizations outside the provisions of the data privacy policy outlined below unless required to do so by law. Dynamic Imaging Solutions is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our customers' personal information and data and this commitment is summarized as follows:
We will not distribute customer information to be used
in mailing lists, surveys, or any other purpose beyond that for which it
was made available.
Data will ONLY be used, accessed, managed, transferred,
disclosed or processed to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was made
available.
Dynamic Imaging Solutions will not request any data
beyond what is necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which our client
requests it to be utilized.
It is the responsibility of our customer to determine
and communicate to Dynamic Imaging Solutions any specific technological,
physical and organizational security measures required to protect data
that is not outlined in this data policy.
Dynamic Imaging Solutions will ensure that any data is
protected in accordance with the security measures communicated to us by
our client
Dynamic Imaging Solutions will ensure that any third
party to whom data is transferred is bound by the applicable terms of this
data policy
Dynamic Imaging Solutions agrees to reasonably
cooperate with requests regarding our clients' data and to amend, destroy,
or return the data upon receiving written instructions to do so from an
authorized customer contact.
Dynamic Imaging Solutions agrees to destroy, or return
all data which is no longer necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which
it was made available unless otherwise instructed.
Dynamic Imaging Solutions Inc. ©2020. All rights Reserved
Web Design and Hosting by Vestra Inet
